## **Dmitrii Dmitrishin**

QA automation engineer

Worked in Medicine Engineering for 6 years, solved different engineering and business tasks including QA work - testing Medicine hardware and software, making reports about it, calibrating. Last year more focused on QA. Testing mobile, web, desktop applications and started working with QA Automation. I can work alone (or as a part of the team) effectively and find solution for any possible problem.

### — Contact Info

Chelyabinsk, Russia github.com/ddmitrishin dmitrishin52@gmail.com +7 919 996 01 64

#### - Skills

Manual QA
QA Automation
iOS/Android
REST API
Java
SQL
Selenide
Jenkins
Selenoid

### — Languages

GitLab/GitHub

#### Russian

Native

JUnit

### **English**

B2. Can speak and translate

### Work Experience

# **Applied Technologies, Ltd.**

QA Engineer | Jul 2021 - Current

- Build from scratch and improve current QA process
- Implemented mindmap in the project for a better understanding of the application
- Development and support of an automated testset on Java-based framework (JUnit
   + Selenide + REST Assured + Allure)

### **Abbott Laboratories**

Technical Ambassador | Aug 2017 - Mar 2021

### **PMTlab**

Engineer | Mar 2016 - Aug 2017

# **Radio Isotopic Production**

Engineer | Mar 2015 - Mar 2016

### Education

## **QA.GURU**

School of Automation Testing Engineers | Apr 2022 - Jul 2022

Improved skills in the technology stack: IntelliJ IDEA, Java, Selenium, Selenide, Selenoid, Allure Report, Gradle, JUnit5, Github, Jenkins, Docker, Allure TestOps, Rest-Assured, Appium, Browserstack, Slack, Telegram, Jira

My Graduate work:

- UI: https://github.com/ddmitrishin/ui\_diploma.git
- API: <a href="https://github.com/ddmitrishin/api diploma.git">https://github.com/ddmitrishin/api diploma.git</a>
- Mobile: <a href="https://github.com/ddmitrishin/mobile\_diploma.git">https://github.com/ddmitrishin/mobile\_diploma.git</a>

My Github profile: https://github.com/ddmitrishin

# **Chelyabinsk State University**

Master of Radiophysics and Electronics | Sep 2009 - Jun 2015